<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cehro India</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Centre for Education and Health Research Organization, founded on 12th March 2012, is a non-profit making autonomous body registered under 1860 Societies Act. It is a social venture formed by the students from NSIT, JAMIA, IIIT etc. and has evolved into an organization where the motto is to help anyone with a will to achieve but is held back by lack of resources.</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment1">CEHRO believes in not letting poverty come in way of success. We strive to make lives better for the impoverished people and the neglected in our society- the migrant laborers and workers involved in other menial jobs, by helping children from these families achieve academically and extracurricularly, so that they can build a better future for themselves.</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment2">For all round development it is essential to consider health as an important parameter. Often health issues come in the way of a child’s education. Hence, we at CEHRO consider it important to sensitize them towards health and hygiene.</string>

    <string name="Our_Vision1">‘Realising the Dream of a Dignified and Respectful Life with the aid of Education and Health to Underprivileged Children.’</string>
    <string name="Our_Vision2"> * To bring slum children enrolled in government schools at par with private school children by giving them remedial classes</string>
    <string name="Our_Vision3"> * To make slum children excel in Computer Education and Spoken English by giving the essential resources</string>
    <string name="Our_Vision4"> * To enroll dropped-out slum children in bridge courses to give them a better future</string>
    <string name="Our_Vision5"> * To promote ‘volunteerism’ and ‘teaching skills’ in slum children through our various programmes</string>
    <string name="Our_Vision6"> * To nurture practice of healthy hygiene activities in slums by engaging doctors and other medical professionals</string>

    <string name="Our_Vision">Overview</string>

    <string name="Over">Overview</string>
    <string name="vision">Our Vision</string>
    <string name="Team">Our Team</string>


    <string name="Prog1">Prog1</string>
    <string name="Prog2">Prog2</string>
    <string name="Prog3">Prog3</string>
    <string name="Prog4">Prog4</string>
    <string name="Prog5">Prog5</string>
    <string name="Prog6">Prog6</string>

</resources>
